我们已经做了我们的扫描,我们也运行了算法 使它不透水。
We have done our scan and we have also run the algorithm that makes it watertight.
然后,我们想做的是,我们想要 切割和操纵网状,
And then after what we want to do is that we want to cut and manipulate the mesh,
取出我们不希望的部分, 而这个我们可以做到这一点 在犀牛。
take out the parts that we don't want, and this we can do it in Rhino.
如果你想只 滑出你的模型 就像在那些地方 它是粗糙的,
If you want to just smooth out your model only like in the places that it is rough,
我建议你使用这个雕塑程序 因为它就像一个刷子 你可以实际上
I recommend that you do use this Sculptris program because it's like a brush and you can actually
在此导入 OBJ。 您可以在这里取一个。 因此导入 Lara , 并且不要在新场景中调整大小 。
import here OBJ. You can take one here. So import Lara and do not resize in a new scene.
这会有点重,因为这个程序 通常工作非常简单
It will be a little bit heavy because this program normally is working with very simple
但好事是你有这把刷子 这样它就能平滑了
very simple things. But the good thing is that here you have this brush so it can smooth.
汝能平定众生.
You can flatten.
这样你就能让它变得非常柔软。你可以看到你想要的力量。
No? So you can make it very soft. You can see the strength that you want.
所以这里,但在这里,我们想 充气一点点,这样我们就可以充气。
So here, but here we want to inflate a little bit so we can inflate. But you don't want to inflate so
不要让这一部分穿进另一部分。这样会形成有问题的网格，最好避免。
that this goes one into the other like that. This is bed. This is a bed mesh. It's better if it's
像更颠簸,不是那样的 因为这意味着 这两块甲壳虫是一边的
like more bumpy and it's not like that because this means that the two meshes are one side the other
如果您想要直接打印3D程序, 这将给您带来问题。 因此在此情况下
and this will give you problems if you want to directly 3D print your program. So in this case
你会做一些像 平滑它出来这样。
you would do like something like smoothen it out like this. So you can actually smooth out the
想要的地方,你可以 让它像完美 在那些地方,如果你
places that you want and you can make it like perfect with this in the places that if your
比如说,我们甚至没有运行算法 来清除这些小的
scan is quite good. This one for example, we didn't even run the algorithm to take out these small
棋子,因为在扫描内,您可以选择像删除小于x数字的棋子。
pieces because inside the scannec you can choose like delete pieces that are smaller than x number.
因此,它会删除它。所以,不管怎样,在你输出它sstl或者你保存它和这个。
So it would have deleted that. So anyway, then after you export it sstl or you save it and this
刚开始,我们只用平滑的网状, 然后,好吧,我们去犀牛和
would be only for smoothening out in the beginning the mesh. Then after, okay, we go to rhino and
为了去犀牛,我们需要导入网状物,所以我输入,是的,
for going to rhino we need to import the mesh. So I import the, yes,
所以输入组或者其实没什么,没关系,我输入会很重。
so import groups or is nothing actually, it doesn't matter. I import that. It will be heavy.
好吧,然后我做缩放 选择的是Zs 这样实际上 它缩放到我想要的地方。
Okay, then I do zoom selected which is zs so that actually it zooms out to where I want.
然后这里我看到一切黑色 因为我右击这里是一个线框 所以基本上
Then here I see everything black because I right click and here it's a wireframe so basically
我想看看它被遮蔽了,它需要一定的渲染
I want to see it's shaded. It will take a render. So here rendered, rendered, rendered with right
点击这个或者鬼魂,我有一个网状的,我有一个网状的,我有一个网状的
click on this or ghost it whatever. So here I have a mesh. Oh, it moved undo. I have a mesh.
第一件事是,我需要了解这是什么尺度。如果是较小的。所以我需要了解。
The first thing is that I need to understand what scale this is. If it is smaller big. So I do
距离,我用眼睛来测量, 但是在它上做一个项目是一瞬间。
distance and I measure with the eye but having project on this thing on it is one of the snaps.
这不考虑第三个维度。所以它只能从这里计算到这里。
This doesn't take into account the third dimension. So it only will calculate from here to here in a
垂直方式,它不会回到第三个维度。所以如果你在这里测量
perpendicular way and it will not go like back in the third dimension. So if you measure here
从这里到这里,你会从这个角度看到 这是横向的,但如果你没有
from here to here you see in the perspective that this is horizontal but if you don't have
工程有时会看到第三个空间, 它不是直的。 因此, 您需要使用工程
project sometimes it sees the third space and it is not straight. So you need to use project
如果您只想要计算两个维度。 因此,这是我从这里到这里测量的工程
if you want to only calculate two dimensions. So this is project I measure from here to here
上面写着它就像一个米5,1,5,5,8,5,5百万
down it says it's like one meter five one thousand five hundred eight five million. So the scale is
没错,这是真正的尺度,如果点击它,我就会看到它是一个网状的。所以实际上,
correct. It is the real scale and this if I click on it down I see that this is a mesh. So actually
我点击这里,它说奶奶现在是一个网格。所以如果我想看看这是什么样的网格,
I click here and it says Nana now it's a mesh. So if I want to see what kind of mesh this is
我将在这里选择,我将在这里朝着这个方向走。
I will go here I will select that I will go here in this direction. So I will do show
裸体放大 裸体放大 裸体放大 裸体放大 裸体
so zoom naked zoom naked. So I select object with naked edges and down it will say the object
物体没有任何裸体的胶片 这意味着它是紧水 意味着有
object doesn't have any naked meshes which means that it is watertight which means that there is
没有像一个洞,因为我们以前做了这个 在松口,我们关闭了它。
no like a hole because we did this before in sconect we closed it. So now this mesh I don't
喜欢操控犀牛的混血儿 但犀牛不是操控混血儿的程序
like to manipulate meshes in Rhino but Rhino is not a program for manipulation of mesh.
所以,我会做网点 内脏实际上 合并到内脏,实际上
So I will do mesh to nerbs which is actually merged to nerb which is actually
因此,它保存了。所以我做网状的内脏。
so it's saved saved. So I do mesh to nerbs.
它会说,你太多的面孔 你会耗尽记忆。
It will say that you have too many faces you will run out of memory. Let's try.
如果它不起作用,它就会有所作为。
And then it doesn't do anything. So yeah good. Yeah it will do something. If it doesn't if it
如果像太高的分辨率 我们就能操纵网格 但最好总是这样
cannot if it's like too high resolution we will manipulate the mesh but it's better always to
将其转换成多面体,是另一种几何学,基本上在犀牛工作.
convert it into poly surface. It's a different kind of geometry basically to work in Rhino.
但有时,也许在你的计算机中,你需要像耐心一样。
But sometimes maybe in your computers you need to have like patience.
它可能会像它一样发生 我想它会做到这一点,它最终会改变它
It will it may happen like it I think it will do it. It will finally convert it.
就像我们这里有纹理 也帮不上什么忙
Also like the fact that we have the the texture here is not helping so much with the
对
yeah.
事实上,这是 部分的渲染。
Actually it's part of the render.
还有
And
另一个程序,而它正在做, 你可以使用的另一个程序是Meshmixer。
the other program while it's doing that the other program that you can use is the mesh mixer.
因此, Meshmixer 也像一个雕刻程序。 您可以看到您可以导入您的
So the mesh mixer also is like a sculpting program. You can see that you can import your
不,然后在这里你可以分析它的力量。
or you can do like the bunny. No and then here you can analyze for example its strength.
你可以看到它更喜欢打破的地方 你可以分析一下
You can see where it is more like keen to break. You can analyze the
您可以按方向测量它。您可以编辑
you can measure it inspected like orient it. You can edit
喜欢不复制 现在,但你可以 雕刻它,所以你知道 像你可以做到这一点。
like not duplicate now but you can sculpt it so you know like you can do.
所以,这是非常好的。
So that's very nice.
我的意思是这种模型 你实际上不能喜欢你 你会打印这种东西。
I mean this kind of model you cannot actually like you you would print this kind of stuff.
不,你不能用这种技术做,最好用3d打印
No you cannot do it with any other kind of technology like this. It's better for 3d printing
但是,是的,你可以在这里用音量的强度来演奏。
but yes you can play with the strength of volume here. You have different brushes that they
他们画画,所以它有点像雕刻, 但它更像 meshes
draw and they draw so it's like a little bit like sculptories but it's more for like meshes
也有一些原始人可以使用。所以这是免费的。
and you have some primitives also that you can use. So it's free. This is free
这样你就可以像分析一样分析了。好吧,这不是真的反应。
and then you can have like the analysis. Okay this is not really responding.
这样你就可以盖章了
So you can stamp it.
我不知道我从这个里面听到什么,有两个有副本,不管怎样,你可以玩这个。
I don't know how I hear in this one. There are two there is a copy. Anyway this one you can play.
他们很好,就像简单的程序, 然后另一个你可以使用的是MeshLab。
They are very nice like easy programs and then another one that you can use is the mesh lab
在那里,MeshLab其实是相当不错的,因为它有这些过滤器。
where the mesh lab actually is quite nice because it has these filters.
因此,这里的MeshLab有一些过滤器,这样你就可以简化网格.
So the mesh lab here it has some filters so you can simplify the mesh.
所以,你可以做一个制服的网状复印 所以它非常烦人。所以在这里。
So you can make like you can make a uniform mesh resampling so it's very annoying. So here
你可以做... 对不起,上面说。
you can do... oh sorry it says here.
因此,它使像... 这是一个过滤器。
So here it makes like... it is a filter.
有趣的是,我放置了非常小的多边形,所以它就像一个大的多边形。
The fun thing is that I put very little polygons so it makes like a big polygon.
它的重塑像一些不正确的东西。
It remeshed like something that is not correct.
它使用不同的算法和库,然后你可以三角化,例如
It's using different algorithms and libraries and then you can triangulate for example
因为现在的网状像更光滑 但你可以做更大的三角形。
because now the mesh is like more smooth but you can make like more bigger triangles.
你可以用滤波器来改变它,总之,这个我会把它干掉的
You can like change it with filters. Anyway so this one I will kill it.
所以它不想进入NERM 而我会直接喜欢操纵它 当作网状,在这里
So it doesn't want to get to NERM and I will directly like manipulate it as a mesh and here
你可以找到所有你能找到的命令... 哦,你看不到,你能看见吗?
you can find all the commands that you can... oh you cannot see there. Can you see them there?
所以你不能在这里看到,事情是... 哦,是的,你可以看到。所以这是所有的命令 一个网。
So you cannot see here that the thing is... oh yes you can see. So here are all the commands for a mesh.
在这里,你像所有命令 对于固体或 命令对于表面。
And here you have like all the commands for solids or the command for surfaces.
就像表面2D一样,关心, 它们是线条,度量,转换的维度。这样你就可以做任何事情。
Like surfaces 2D, cares, which are lines, dimension for measuring, transforming. So you can do everything
在犀牛从顶端的栏杆上,但是你也可以用图标从侧边栏做一切事情,或者你
in Rhino from the top bar but you can also do everything from the sidebar with icons or you
因此,有三种方法可以做同样的事情。
can also write everything. So there are three ways to do the same thing. So in this case what I want
要做的是,我想做一个盒子, 我想把这个盒子在这里, 这个盒子需要像
to do is that I want to make a box and I want to put this box here and this box needs to be like
我用这个图标做了,但如果你愿意,也可以写盒子
bigger. And then I will... I did it with here with this icon but if you want you can also write box
举例来说,如果你想的话,你可以去坚固的盒子。有三种方法也是一样的。
for example and if you want you can go solid box. It's the same thing with three ways. So then after
我会把盒子移到这里,基本上,这是... 如果你看到这个是...
I will move the box here and basically this is... if you see this one is... if you see down it says
所以这两个人不是朋友,他们什么都做不了。
it is an extrusion and this one is a mesh. So these two people are not friends. They cannot do anything
就像你无法加入他们一样,你不能割断他们,不能...
together. Like you cannot join them, you cannot cut them, you cannot... because they are different
一种是几何类型,另一种是另一种几何类型。
families. One is one kind of type of geometry and the other is one other kind of type of geometry.
因此,基本上, meshes 可以被操纵与 meshes, 固体与固体, 表面与表面 和所有
So basically meshes can be manipulated with meshes, solids with solids, surfaces with surfaces and all
你无法在网状和网状之间做任何事情。
the families all... all together. You cannot do anything between a solid and a mesh. So what you
需要做的就是把这个盒子转换成网状。所以我会把它编成网状,然后它问我如何
need to do is that to do this box convert it into a mesh. So I will mesh it and then it asks me how
您想要的许多多边形。我默认。所以我基本上转换了固体的几何形状。
many polygons you want. I do it default. So basically I convert the geometry of the solids
我把拉伸实体的几何转换成网格；其他网格也可以这样处理。
to... of the extrusion to the geometry of a mesh and I could have done the same for the mesh
我之前告诉你的这个命令 是网状神经 但是多边形太多了
with this command that I showed you before which is mesh to nerves but it's too many polygons so
基本上我不会。所以现在,如果我点击我有两个东西,一个是挤压,一个是网状。
basically I will not. So now here if I click I have two things one extrusion and one mesh.
其中一个在同一个地方。所以我选择了挤压,然后删除它。所以现在这个是。
One inside the other at the same spot. So I choose the extrusion and I delete it. So now this one is
这个和那个现在都是网格。先保存，记得经常保存。
a mesh and this one is a mesh. So let's see... so now I will save that first always try to save.
好吧,现在我会尝试 做一个布尔行动。
Okay and then now what I will try to do is that I will try to make a Boolean operation.
布尔操作是您有两个对象 A 和 B 的操作, 然后您可以进行布尔操作
Boolean operations are the operations that you have two objects A and B and then you can do Boolean
结合。 这样您就可以做一个对象 C , 或者您可以进行布尔分割。 因此您有 A 。
union. So you can do one object the object C or you can do a Boolean split. So you have the A
没有这部分,没有这部分的B 和作为两者交汇点的小对象
without this part the B without this part and the small object which is the intersection of the two
所以说A减B,所以只有这个
as a C or you can make the difference of them. So you say A minus B so it's only this one. So there
是不同的操作,我们叫布林 操作在这里,你可以看到你有
are different operations as we call Boolean operations and here as you can see you have
布尔差异 布尔分裂 布尔结合 一般来说我个人更喜欢这样做
Boolean difference, Boolean split, Boolean union. In general personally I prefer to do
布尔分裂。所以我拥有我所有的开始,但分裂,然后我删除我拥有的
Boolean split. So I have everything that I had in the beginning but split and then I delete what I have
所以,在这种情况下,我想做一个布尔分裂,但为网状。
but you can try all of them. So in this case I want to do a Boolean split but for mesh
我需要选择boolean的网状分裂,它只为网状分裂。
I need to choose mesh Boolean split which is there. It's only for the meshes.
我想用盒子分给珍妮,请输入,现在它会
So what do I want to split? I want to split Jenny with the box. Enter. So now it will
计算一下,你可以看到网状布林分裂在进展中,希望它能分裂出来。
calculate for a moment down you can see mesh Boolean split in progress and hopefully it will split it.
所以你可以把Jenny转换成NERB 你不需要做网格盒 你可以做的
So you have been able to convert Jenny into NERBs you don't need to do the mesh box you can just do
框中。是的,最好用普通命令拆分布尔。是的,所以它这样做似乎是因为
boxes. Yes and best Boolean split with the normal command. Yeah so it seems that it did it because
现在它不再计算了,让我们来看看珍妮。
now it's not calculating anymore so let's see Jenny. So Jenny is without the base that's cool.
另一件事是,我们现在可以删除它。
The other thing is that so now we can delete that. The cool thing with the Boolean which is a
修剪之间的区别,因为你也可以修剪,这是命令修剪。
difference between trim because you can also cut trim it's the command trim. The cool thing with the
布尔是它会使它坚固 所以它会关闭它。你会有一个表面是封闭的。
Boolean is that it will make it solid so it will close this. You will have a surface that is closed
也就是说,你的模型仍然紧缺。如果你做了修剪,你就会被剪除,但是...
which means that your model is still watertight. If you did a trim you would be cutting but then
它会打开,你下面没有地表,你要我修剪一下,这样你就可以
it will be open and you would have no surface under you. You want me to do a one trim so that you
是的,它保持空洞,所以你只会看到 就像你拥有
can see the difference? Yes it stays hollow so you will only see like as if you had the
彼得没有想念这个身体的表面 但里面什么都没有,这不合适
peter miss no the one surface of this body but inside there was nothing and this is not appropriate
用于操作 c3d 打印或任何东西, 基本上有您可以完成的命令
for manipulation c3d printing or anything and basically there are commands that you can do
类似命令的盖子,它把盖子放在打开的物体上,但这只针对那些物体
like the command the cap which puts like caps on the open objects but this is only for objects that
如果它像一个弯曲的表面,你可以 关闭盖子是行不通的。
they are flat. If it's like a curved surface that you can you need to close cap will not work.
现在,我会做同样 在这里和这里 也许因为我不想这样
Now I will do the same here and here maybe because I don't want this
举个例子,我不想要这只手。
I don't want this hand for example.
所以,让我们做这个缩放 选定的输入,所以我可以 一点点旋转她
So yes so let's do this zoom selected enter so I can a little bit rotate her
这样她就直了或者喜欢
so that it she's straight or like
碞钩ê 礛и碞硂暗 ⁇  琌иぃи材维
like there and then I can make a box here but then you see I cannot see the third dimension I go
我在这里设计,这样你就可以有一个这样的一个 我设计一个盒子在这个侧 一个维度,所以
and I design here so you can have like a this one I design a box in this side for one dimension so
然后在这个屏幕的前屏幕上显示另一个维度
and then in this screen front screen for the other dimension basically
盒子必须从网状物上放出来
it's mandatory that the box it is bigger goes out from the thing from the mesh
因为布林比较容易计算 所以好,我这样做
because the Boolean is easier calculated so okay I do that
然后,我把它们粘好,然后我真正选择
and then I will mesh them okay and then I will actually select
挤压和删除挤压,因为在犀牛,我可以选择可以选择的对象的家族
extrusions and delete the extrusions because in Rhino I can select families of objects I can
选择 meshes 然后它会选择一切 或者我可以选择点 然后它会说
select meshes and it will select everything or I can select points and then it will say
这件事情没有分数,没有分数,反正好,然后我会网起来
there are no points there are no points in this thing okay anyway and then I will mesh
Boolean又分了 我想分了 因为它总是问犀牛会问你你怎么做的
Boolean split again I want to split this because it asks always Rhino will ask you what do you
想要做,你必须读到,你不必读它 说选择 meshes 所有的多孔的表面
want to do and you have to read that no you have to read it says select meshes all porous surfaces
,然后按下输入,您想要用它拆分什么
to split and then press enter enter with what do you want to split it with this
所以我会再次等待 最后在这里我得到了这个 这样我就可以删除它,然后我会
so then I will wait again and then finally here I have this so I can delete that and then I will
做同样的事情,我想分这个 与那个输入,现在它有点切
do the same with I want to split this with that enter so now that it's a little bit more cut
好吧,我会保存它
okay I will save it
然后,我会再次尝试做它 网状神经,或也许没有 它不重要,没有
and then I will try again to do it mesh to nerves or maybe no it doesn't matter no no
所以没关系,所以如果我现在想放这个模型
so it's okay so if I want now to put this model in
切片器 我将提交所选导出文件 。 我选择要进行导出的东西, 我总是要进行导出
a slicer I will file export selected I select what I want to do export and I always do export
选择只是不要问,为什么只是这样做 因为有很多问题 如果你只是导出
selected just don't ask why just do it like that because there are many problems if you just export
因为现场还有别的东西, 然后它就像一个大烂摊子 对于3d打印机和
because there are other things in the scene and then it's like a big mess for the 3d printer and
总是被选中导出, 我选择您想要导出的东西, 然后我可以导出为 obg
just always export selected and I select what you want to export and then I can export it as obg
所以这是珍妮切
so this is Jenny cut
在这里,你只是离开它,因为它不是
and here you just leave it as it is don't
嗯,是的,你可以输出它 作为神经 同时,现在
uh yeah you can export it as nerves also in any case now
是啊,我们要做它作为物体 所以我现在去切片机 核聚变360
yeah we we are going to do it as object so now I go to slicer for fusion 360
基本上说
and um basically
最好能用雕塑来打开 也看看它是否平滑
yeah it would be nice for example this model to open it in sculptures and see also smooth it out
喜欢什么 喜欢它有凸起或喜欢 一点点与托什喜欢触摸它,因为
like whatever like it has bumps or like a little bit with a tush like to touch it because
伤疤上方的伤痕 听起来更难受 所以珍妮不要紧水
we from the scar need to come sound like more bumpy so Jenny no water tight
珍妮切开,然后这里会发生什么是
Jenny cut open and then here what will happen is that
如果你想做珍妮的所有身体 我们应该拆开它 并有两个文件 因为激光
if you want to do all the body of Jenny we should split it and have two files because the laser
切割器是600米的1米 所以,你不能做高于1米的 基本上,当你想要
cutter is one meter by 600 so you cannot do higher than one meter so basically when you want to
做你的钱团队,你必须做一个盒子 一个米 完全放你想要的部分
do your money team you have to make a box that is one meter exactly put the part that you want to
进去切掉其余的 因为激光切割器是一米多 如果你想做
do inside and cut the rest because the laser cutter is one meter and if you want to do the
分两部分,然后分两部分,然后分两部分,然后加入
two parts then you have to split them and do them separately and then join them
当你在激光切割机里组装的时候
when you assemble it in this laser cutter
是啊,所以我用OBG,但如果你可以导入 STL在犀牛,也许它没有纹理 所以,
yeah so I use the OBG but if you can import the STL in Rhino maybe it doesn't have the texture so
也许它比较轻,但部落 并不那么确定 微小的物体会更多
maybe it's lighter but tribal that's not so for sure the scant object will be more
重过人的身体,你知道,因为 微小的物体从...
heavy than the make human body you know because the scant object became out from the
点云是三角化的,然后有一个算法 运行和关闭了洞,
point cloud that was triangulated and then there was an algorithm that ran and closed the holes and
你不知道它是否正确关闭了它们
you don't know if it closed them correctly so
你可以现在做它,也许
can you do it now yeah maybe
我将说的方式
the way I will say
所以如果我们想让珍妮做正确的尺寸 我们就会砍掉她的头
so if we want to do Jenny the correct size we would cut her head
所以为了切掉她的头 我们最好不要像切成直线 不切成直线
so in order to cut her head it's better if we cut it not like straight no if we cut it for example
喜欢
like
像这样,不
like this no
不,这很成问题,其实是个很好的例子
no this will be very problematic is a good example actually to see
所以如果我想这样砍她的头 或者也许有点像
so if I want to cut her head like that or maybe a little bit like
我旋转它,我移动它 有点像那样 是的,所以这个我会挤出它。
I rotate it and I move it a little bit like that yeah so this one I will extrude it
像这样,然后我把水面挤出来
like this and then I will extrude the surface like that
哦,是的,然后我就把它压碎 好删除挤压多层表面
oh yeah and then I will just mash it okay delete the extrusion the poly surface
然后把这个和这个分开
and then mesh boolean split this one with this one
然后，
and
那样吧
then
是的,然后你看这里有点不妙 所以我需要继续打扫,但是...
yes and then you see here is a little bit not good so I need to continue cleaning but
我会去前视线,然后从这里排出一条线,我就会排出一条线
I will go to the front view and I will make a line from here and it will be I will make a line
这里有一个曲线 从这里多线 从这里,它会是1000, 这是一个米的哇
here a curve from here polyline from here and it will be 1000 which is one meter wow
所以,现在你需要告诉我们 你的身高之前,我砍你的头
so now you need to tell us your height before I cut your head
然后，
and
珍妮在哪里,你需要告诉我们 你的身高之前,我切。
where is Jenny you need to tell us your height before I cut
对
yes
喜欢从这里
like from here
到这里
to here
155 155 0 (韩语)
155 155 0
啊,不,我没有做正确 对不起,我会再做一次 所以我做了一个多线 从这里
ah no I didn't do correctly sorry I will do it again so I make a polyline from here
到这里,我会写155 0 点击和完成好 所以我不看到多线 原因我
to here and I will write 155 0 enter click and done okay so I don't see the polyline the reason I
没有看到多线是因为我有它 被渲染,线是不能 渲染,如果我有
don't see the polyline is because I have it in rendered and lines cannot be rendered if I have
在钢丝框里,我可以看到它 这样遮荫,我可以看到它幽灵,我可以看到它,但做了线条
it in wireframe I can see it so shade it I can see it ghosted I can see it but rendered lines
反正是无法制造的 所以这个是你的高度 所以基本上我会给你放大一点
cannot be rendered anyway so this one is your height so basically I will scale you a little bit
缩放
scale
我会把像 从这里到这里和这里 好,所以我做了一条线 正确大小
and I will put like from here to here and here okay so I made a line in the correct size
然后,我抓住它,我缩放 它的参考线,所以现在我可以删除
and then I grabbed it and I scale it with a reference of the line so now I can delete that
现在我可以做这条线 从这里。
and now I can make this line which will be from here
在这里,一个米是激光切割器的大小,好吗?
to here one meter which is the size of the laser cutter okay
并随后
and then
然后,实际上,我需要做一个盒子 这将是这个盒子, 对于第三个维度,我刚刚去
and then actually I need to make a box which will be this box and for the third dimension I just go
从角度来说,我确实喜欢, 也许我只是不需要做 像完全一个米表,因为它是
to perspective and I do like that maybe I just don't need to do like exactly one meter because it's
正好一个米的激光切割器 所以它就像留下一些边距 这样我就可以移动这个
exactly one meter the laser cutter so it's good like to leave some margin so I can move this
前面我可以移动这个移动50毫米 所以它就像我有一些空间,然后我
front I can move this move this by 50 millimeters so it's like I have like some space and then I
将匹配框,然后
will match the box and then
哦,是的,如果你想做 整个身体,那么你只得 分开它
oh yeah if you want to do the whole body then you would have to separate it only
然后把切片机装好 然后组装起来 就像激光切割一样
and you put the slicer but then you will assemble it they will be like laser cutting
一半和激光切掉另一半 然后你必须想办法加入他们
half and laser cutting the other half and then you have to try to find a way to join them
更复杂 所以这是网状的
which is more complicated and anyway so this is the mesh
在这里,我删除了挤压,所以不要担心 如果你第一次没有得到它
and then here I delete the extrusion so don't worry if you don't get it for the first time
因为我们会做很多次,你会学到的 我想我正在录制会议
because we will do it so many times that you will learn it and I think that I'm recording the session
所以我今晚会寄给你 所以用我想要的来分我想要的
so I will send it to you tonight and so mesh boolean split what I want to split this with what I want
把它和那个分开,然后我还 采取,所以实际上我还得在这里打扫
to split it with that and then I also take that so actually I have to still clean here
为了能够在这里看到一个错误
and in order to be able to so here you see that there is an error
这是不好的,因为这个会出来 在切片机这样基本上
this is bad because this will come out in the slicer so basically
我会告诉你怎么做 所以这里最好切掉这个
I will tell you how to do it so here it would be good to cut this
所以为了切开这个,我会去正确的视野 是的,现在我会切开这个这样。
so in order to cut this I will go to the right view yes and now I will cut this so
这么说吧
so
不是这个拉伸方向；当前方向不符合我的需要。
extrude no no an extrude but it's a it's extruding in a direction that I don't want
所以,我要做的是 我会在这里说方向
so what I will do is that I will say here direction
我会告诉你,方向是 从这里到那里
and I will tell that the direction is from here and then to there
所以在这里对不起,所以在这里的问题 是,这一个非常小 在后面这里
so here sorry so here the problem is that this one is very small in the backside here
它不会有点像出去,它会失败 所以我需要移动它一点点
it doesn't go a little bit like out and it will fail so I need to move it a little bit
然后,我将不得不挤压这个表面 因为每次我想挤出的东西
and then I will have to extrude this surface because every time I want to extrude something
这就像选择什么样的几何 我拥有,然后我再做一个网状
it's like selecting what kind of geometry I have and then I will do a mesh again
然后我就把布利恩分了 不许把布利恩分了
and then I will Boolean split this one no mesh Boolean split this one with this one
是啊,所以让我们把这个拿出来,现在在这里
yeah so let's take this out and now here
这儿
here
好吧,它不是完美的,所以我会喜欢
well it's not perfect so I will do like
是啊,我会做另一行 不,没关系,它也没关系 所以它离开了,因为我
yeah I will do another line no no it's okay and it's also okay so it left so because my
我的音量,我做的盒子没有那么大 它留下了这个,这是不好的
my volume that I the box that I made was not so big it left this and this is bad
所以基本上我会再做一次 你知道 做一个大的不,因为
so basically I will I will have to do it again you know like make a big no because
你看,你在这里看到, 重做删除重做,哦,不重做 这些他们在一起
they you see that you see here redo delete redo redo oh no redo redo these ones they are together
我要是想拆开他们,就想拼命组队
it's one thing if I want to split them I would do like I would try and group
最好把这个盒子放大一个维度的1d
no it's better it's better actually to make this box bigger scale 1d in one dimension
所以基本上从这里到这里, 使它更大 现在,我会网布林分裂
so basically from here to here and make it bigger and now I will mesh Boolean split
这个有我不知道,但对不起 伙计们,它在这里,我再次在一起 编辑重制版的表面
this one with I don't know but sorry guys it's here I it's together again edit redo extrude surface
重做网格重做删除此事项, 现在只缩放一个维度
redo mesh redo delete the thing and now scale only in one dimension
因为我只想从这里到这里 再把布林的网格放大
because I only want to scale in this dimension from here to here and there and then mesh Boolean
把这个和这个分开
split this one with this one
所以它没有看到它不做 它有一个错误 它使像 发生在这里
so it doesn't you see it doesn't do it it has an error it makes like so what happens is that here
基本上,我太低了,我需要把这个多一点。
I basically am too much down and I need to put this a little bit more up
所以,让我们看看更好的
so let's see better
在正确的视野中,发生了什么,所以没关系,这应该很好
here in the right view what is happening so okay this should be fine
我实际上可以移动它 直到在这里 是的,所以, mesh Boolean 分裂 mesh Boolean 分裂
I actually can move it until here yeah so mesh Boolean split mesh Boolean split
这个和这个一起
this one with this one
好,让我看看
okay so let's see
好吧,所以下次头发应该更紧
okay so next time the hair should be tighter
不,没关系,反正我现在要选择文件导出
no it's it's okay anyway now I will file export selected
和珍妮更多的剪辑SNBG
and Jenny more cut SNBG
好吧,你在这里看到它说输出网状纹理坐标 我们不希望的纹理
okay so here you see it says export mesh texture coordinates we don't want the texture
所以我就把这个拿出来
so I just take this out
现在我们可以回到这里,这样
and now we can go back to here so
所以这里我们有珍妮 当你打开它
so here we have Jenny and the thing is that when you open that
首先,你看到,这是两个 它就像它把它像水平 这就像
program first of all you see that it's the both it's like it put it like horizontal this is like
你看,它把它像另一个方向 当你打开软件的时候你选择它。
you see it's put it like in the other direction this you choose it when you open the software
但我选择了喜欢的Y 就像我选择的这个物体的长边是Y,所以它
but I chose like the the Y like I chose like the the long side of this object is the Y so it
不管怎么说,打开它,所以我们基本上需要 在这里说,我们是在工作。
opened it like down anyway so basically we need to go here and say that we are we were working in
10毫米,然后我们就得到这里 把这个装在原来的尺寸
millimeters and then we need to go here and put that we want this in this original size
因为它自动打开 并有它逃跑
because it automatically open and have it to escape
所以现在我们可以看到,这是高度 它实际上说宽度,因为它是水平的。
so now we can see that this is the height actually it says width because it's horizontal
所以这是完美的,那么接下来我们需要做的是 我们需要按这个设置的事情
so that's perfect then the next thing we need to do is that we need to press this setting thing
制造环境,这是非常重要的,因为我们需要 定义什么是大小
manufacturing settings and it is very important because we need to define what is the size of
我们要用的材料 上面的纸牌有多大?
the material that we're going to use so what is the size of the boards the card on the so here
点击这里的设置时, 下到这里就可以工作了
down when you click here up in the settings then if you go down here you can put that you work
10毫米,你可以说纸板的尺寸是1米,就是1千米
millimeters and you can put that the size of the cardboard is one meter which is one thousand
以六百计 板子的厚度是四 基本上就是激光切割器的大小
by six hundred and the thickness of the board is four so basically the size of the laser cutter
我们将要购买的板子的大小 是六百公分之一的
is the size of the boards that we are going to buy which is one meter by six hundred and the
我们将要购买的板子的厚度是四,比如说,这里会发生什么?
thickness of the boards that we are going to buy will be four for example so what will happen here
现在这是好的,所以这是 习惯,你必须在这里 选择的习惯,你
and now it's this is okay so this is the custom you have to go here and select the custom that you
放下,在这里你可以选择构造技术 所以这里有堆叠的切片
put down and here you can choose the construction techniques so here you have the stacked slices
比如说,在这里它会做所有堆叠的切片 然后你可以得到组装计划
for example so here it will make all the stacked slices and then you can get the assembly plans
它可以想象你需要怎样组装它 你看见了
and it will visualize how you need to assemble it you see
嗯,这个是超容易的,但你看,它需要像
well this one is super easy but you see that it needs like
这些板子都不好,所以我们不这样做 然后你有插合的切片
all these boards and it's not good so we will not do that and then you have the interlocked slices
所以,你在这里看到,这是所有红色的原因
so you see here that is all red why
为什么都是红的?
why is it all red
是空的吗?
is it empty
基本的问题是 当它是红色的, 它就像它意味着 它不是你做它
basically the problem is that when it's red it's like it means that it doesn't you cannot make it
这是因为这个精灵是一米五十, 我的板是一米,所以它不适合
and the reason here is because this genie is one meter fifty and my boards are one meter so it doesn't fit
笵
you know so
我可以在这里做精灵一米,但这就像一个缩放版
I could do the genie one meter here but this is like a scaled version
不,我可以在那里放大, 但我不想在那里放大,因为它意味着所有的东西
no I can scale it there but I don't want to scale it there because it means that everything that
我之前算过,是错的 所以基本上,如果我放大它 它非常好在干燥的土地上
I had calculated before is wrong so basically I if I scale it it's very good in dry land
当你在制造的最后一步 像你去激光切割前的一刻
when you are in the last step of the fabrication that like one moment before you go to laser cut
最好不要像一般的大小一样 设计它和在设计时的大小
it's better not to scale in general like if you design it and you scale it when you're designing
要知道,如果它不适合上周 所以我会在这里把它像更小
you know but if it doesn't fit for last week so here I will make it like even smaller
所以这是像小精灵一样的密尼翁
so this is a mignon like a small genie
因此,您可以在此选择
so here you can actually select
仍然有不合适 因为它把它放在这个方向,所以
there's still doesn't fit because it puts it in this direction so
是的,它把它放在600,因为它有点问题 软件
yeah it puts it in the 600 because it's a little bit problematic the software
因为它会随着我横向导入它 并且它想做横向,所以它无法理解
because it will as I imported it horizontal and it wants to do horizontal so it cannot understand
它可以旋转它 在程序 但我可以做的是 我可以在这里,我可以放
that it can rotate it in the program but what I could do is that I could go here and I can put
这是600,这是1000,你看
that this is 600 and this is 1000 you see
好吧,现在我们可以放 多少,如果我们想在这里,然后我们也可以
okay so now we we can put like more or less if we want here and then we can also
因此,我们也可以改变 切片方向,如果你想让它喜欢
so we can also change the slice direction if you want to make it like
在此更改学位
change the degree here
你可以玩 方向的切片
and you can play with the direction of the slices
在不同的轴上
in the different axis
这么说吧
so
因为某种原因,你也可以修改表格 如果你使用这个技术
for some reason modify form and you can also I mean if you're using this technique
在这里你得到 组装步骤,所以
here you get the assembly steps so
这么说吧
so
你可以选择塑料游戏 只用于视觉 所以我想在这里发生什么
you can choose plastic play would only for visualization so what happens here I want
告诉你一些非常重要的事 我完成
to tell you something very very important and I finish
这个,你看,它有两个插槽 一个在这里,一个在这里,但这个是
this one you see that it has two slots one here and one here but this one is
小的,所以没关系的 这一个进入很好,这一个进入很好
small so it's okay doesn't matter this one enters nicely this one enters nicely
这个进好,这个进好,这个进好,这个进好,这个进好,这个进好
this one enters okay this one enters but this one that has this hole here
我的意思是实际上它不能输入 它是错误的 程序基本上有一个bug是没有的
I mean actually it cannot enter it's wrong the program basically has a bug that is not
完美编程,所以有时候,如果你有 喜欢的东西是上下
perfect the program so sometimes it's if you have like something that is up and down it makes
喜欢两个插槽,但实际上 你不能把它 因为你需要你 需要
like two slots but actually in reality you cannot put it because you would need you would need to
有个连续的插槽 用来从下到上传出去 好好照顾好这个
have like one continuous slot for passing it from down all up so just take care that this
如果发生这种事 因为如果发生这种事 我们就在犀牛打开它
if this thing happens because if this happens this happens we just open it in Rhino
我们删除你所知道的路径 因为这里不能进入三个插槽
and we delete that path you know like because here it cannot enter in the three slots it's if
我是说,如果是三块的话,就会像一块大块,如果是三块的话
I mean it will be like one big piece if it's if it's three if it is three pieces it enters
但是,如果这是一个大片 有时程序认为 你可以把它这样,但你
but if it is one big piece sometimes the program thinks that you can put it like that but it you
不能只顾着这两个档子的事,当它发生的时候,我的意思是,我不知道是不是
cannot so just beware of these two slots thing when it happens I mean here I don't know if it's
只有一小块或大块,但有时 如果它有问题,所以它是小块
only a small piece or big but sometimes and if it is if it has problems so it's small piece
如果它有问题,所以这个 是的,你可以把它 你可以看到它读 就像我们以前一样
if it has problems so this one yeah you can put it you can see it read like as we did before
就是这样
that's it
在这里的账户里,你可以选择 通过距离,你把每一个距离,或者你可以只是
here in the account so you can choose by distance and you put every the distance or you can just
说好,我要10个朝这个方向,两个朝这个方向,你看
and say okay I want 10 in this direction and two in this direction you see
然后,你也可以做 光圈切片,这是如此
and then you can also do the radial slices which is so
有点困难,但有一次我做了,你也可以做
but it's a little bit difficult but it's nice one time I did ah and you can also
在此选择此孔的大小 。
choose this size of this hole here modify form you can make it hollow you see
所以,但你不想 使这个空洞 因为这将是非常困难 组装
so but you don't want to make this hollow because it will be very difficult to assemble
但是如果你在做堆叠的切片 你想把像灯在里面
but if you were doing stacks stacked slices and you want to put like a light inside
然后你会把它变成空洞
then you would make it hollow
然后得到植物 然后得到红色的一层 即雕刻
and then you get the plants and then you you get one layer in red that is the engraving
用于激光切割器的层 和蓝色的层 用于切割,然后你
layer for the laser cutter and one layer that is the blue one that is for cutting and then you
定义用于雕刻的激光切割器中的功率和速度以及功率和速度。
define the power and the speed in the laser cutter for engraving and the power and the
激光切割的速度,我想就这样
speed for laser cutting I think that's it